Contact

sheilalebrun@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/sheila-lebrunjames-cmsrn-a793a743 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

BLS

Medical/Surgical Inpatient

Sheila Lebrun-James, CMSRN

Regional Manager, Clinical Performance Capital Area Washington D.C. Metro Area

Summary

Experienced Hospitalist RN with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care field. Responsible for the management and improvement of HCAPHS, Case mix index, readmissions, length of stay and quality indicators (CAUTI, CLABSI and C-diff).

Experience

Sound Physicians

4 years

Regional Manager, Clinical Performance April 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months)

Hospitalist RN

July 2016 - April 2018 (1 year 10 months)

Alexandria, Virginia

As a Hospitalist RN daily functions include monitoring and analyzing data performance of physicians at site level while also implementing initiatives to improve Case Mix Index, Length of Stay and Patient experience.

St Agnes Hospital

Clinical Unit Coordinator

November 2011 - May 2016 (4 years 7 months)

Clinical Unit Coordinator

St Joseph's Medical Center- Towson, MD

Registered Nurse

October 2011 - September 2012 (1 year)

Behavioral Health Unit

Coney Island Hospital

Registered Nurse

January 2010 - April 2011 (1 year 4 months)

Charge Nurse Psychiatric Emergency

Education

Walden University

Master of Public Health (M.P.H.), Public Health · (2015 - 2017)

Long Island College Hospital of Brooklyn School of Nursing Associates Degree in Nursing, Nursing · (2007 - 2009)

Brooklyn College

Bachelor's Degree, Psychology · (2003 - 2006)